嘿  罗斯
Hey,Ross.
真高兴有人在这里
I'm so glad someone's here.
你可以帮我把拉链拉起来吗
Could you zip me up?
当然可以  谢谢
Sure.  Thank you.
你相信从我家到这里的路上
Can you believe no one between my apartment and here..
竟然没人愿意帮我拉拉链吗
offered to do that for me?
人啊
People.
你穿这么漂亮做什么呢
So why are you so dressed up?
麦克要来接我去约会
Mike's picking me up for a date.
交往得如何  是不是越来越认真了
How's that going? Is it getting serious?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
我是蛮喜欢他的
I mean,I like him.
但是我还没有准备好
But am I ready
让我这么优秀的人退出单身市场
to take my Grade A loins off the meat market?
我不太确定
I'm not quite sure.
我真的很欣赏你的约会态度
You know,I really admire your whole dating attitude.
真是很健康
It's so healthy.
我总是在想  会不会进展太快了
I'm always like,"Is this moving too fast?
会不会进展太慢了 这将怎么发展呢
Is this moving too slow? Where's this going?"
我知道  你就像是个戏剧女王
I know. You are a bit of a drama queen.
你真是太厉害了
You're so much better off.
男朋友一个接着一个  享受乐趣
You just go from guy to guy having fun..
完全不担心没有认真的结局
and not worrying that it never turns into anything serious.
我不敢说"完全不"
I wouldn't say "never."
有一次有个男的
You know,there is that guy.
好吧  那个
Okay,well,what about..?
总该有个人吧
Okay,there's gotta be someone.
根本就没有  我就说吧
There isn't! That's what I'm saying.
噢  天啊  你说的没错
Oh,my God,you're right!
我知道  瞧你现在
I know. And yet,here you are,
又可以开始新恋情啦
all ready for the next date.
真不敢相信  我之前都没有意识到这点
I can't believe I never realized this before.
我已经三十几岁了
I'm in my 30s,
却从来没有爱情长跑过
and I've never been in a longterm relationship.
噢  天啊  我是有什么毛病
Oh,my God,what's wrong with me?
不不不
No, no, no.
你没有什么毛病
There's nothing wrong with you.
我是说  你不像是那种
I mean,you don't strike me as
急着想要结婚的人
the type of person that wants to get married.
我想结婚
I want to get married!
别这样  拜托别因为我而哭
No,please.. Please don't cry because of me.
我根本不知道我在说什么
I don't know what I'm talking about,okay?
我都离婚三次了
I've been divorced three times.
至少你结过婚
At least you've been married.
噢  天啊  我竟然羡慕起罗斯了
Oh,my God! I want to trade lives with Ross?!
菲比
Phoebe.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事  要跟你约会太兴奋了
Nothing. I'm excited about our date.
麦克  这位是罗斯·盖勒
Mike,this is Ross Geller.
罗斯  这位是麦克
Ross,this is Mike..
对不起  我没有听清楚
Sorry,I didn't catch that.
麦克·汉尼根
Mike Hanigan.
罗斯·盖勒  嘿
Ross Geller.  Hey.
你确定准备好了吗
So are you sure you're ready to go?
我看起来怎样
How do I look?
你皮包里有小镜子吗  没有
Do you have a compact in your purse?  No.
你看起来棒极了
You look great.
《老友记》  第九季 第4集  鲨鱼
Friends S09E04 The One With The Sharks
嘿  乔伊
Hey,Joey.
那个女的就是不转过来
This girl won't turn around.
我无法判断她是不是很性感  你觉得呢
I can't tell if she's hot or not. What do you think?
乔伊  我不会跟你一起把女性物化的
Joey,I am not going to objectify women with you.
但是如果她的脸跟她的屁股一样棒的话
But if her face is as nice as her ass..
妈啊  好的  谢谢
Mama!  All right. Thanks.
你有跟钱德勒通电话了吗
Have you talked to Chandler?
他这周末要留在塔尔萨
He has to stay in Tulsa this weekend.
为什么 我不知道  有工作要做
How come?  I don't know. He has to work.
要赶那个什么...
There's some big rush on the..
讨厌  总有一天我该开始
Damn it. One of these days I'm gonna have to start
认真听他讲工作的事了
listening when he talks about his job.
你何不飞过去给他个惊喜呢
Why don't you fly out there and surprise him?
或许我应该飞过去
Maybe I will go.
我们可以来个二度小蜜月
We'll have a little second honeymoon
地点就在塔尔萨的饭店
at the Tulsa Ramada.
你应该带你那件黑色透明性感内衣
You should bring your black seethrough teddy
带吊带裤袜的那件
with the attached garters.
你怎么知道我有那件呢
How do you know I have one of those?
本来不知道  现在知道了
Didn't until just now.
性感  不性感
Hot. Not hot.
性感
Hot!
什么
Excuse me?
我说我觉得你很性感
I said that I think you're hot.
而现在我糗死了
And.. now I'm embarrassed.
我以为你是说"嗨"
I thought you said "hi."
如果是那样就好了
That would've been better.
我来试试看  嗨  我是乔伊
I'll try that. Hi,I'm Joey.
我是海莉
I'm Hayley.
通常我不约
Look,I don't normally ask out
在咖啡店遇到的女生出去
women that I meet in coffeehouses.
祝你健康
Gesundheit.
反正  我很乐意跟你出去
Anyway..  I would love to go out with you.
真的吗  太棒了
Really? Great.
我有我有开口约你吗
Did I..? Did I actually ask you?
由你说话的方式
That's just where you were going.
我就猜得到你要做什么
I figured I'd help you out.
你不像是那种经常这样的男生吧
You don't seem like the kind of guy who does this a lot?
约会还好吗  糟透了
So how'd the date go?  Well,it was awful.
每次我想到你说的话  我就哭了
Every time I thought about what you said,I cried.
他还没打来吗
So he hasn't called?
你会打给这种女的吗
Would you call this girl:
"谢谢美好一晚"
"Thanks for.. a lovely.. evening"?
我觉得糟透了  全都是我的错
Now I feel terrible. This is all my fault.
你知道更糟的是什么吗
You know what you should feel terrible about?
那男的原本可能是我认真交往的对象
This could have been my serious guy.
他很体贴  聪明又风趣
He was sweet and smart and funny.
你知道要遇到这样的男生有多难吗
You know how hard it is to meet a guy like that?
我们的确是很稀有
We are a rare breed.
晚餐实在太棒了
What a great dinner.
再次谢谢你让我
Thanks again for letting me
吃最后一块蛋糕
have that last piece of cake at the restaurant.
不用客气  我要去煮咖啡
You're welcome again. I'm gonna go make some coffee.
你要什么呢 你有蛋糕吗
Can I get you anything?  Do you have any cake?
真是进行的太顺利了
So this is going pretty good.
晚餐很棒  我们有许多共同点
Dinner was nice. We've got a lot in common.
"维多莉亚的秘密"性感内衣目录
Victoria 's Secret.
我们甚至喜欢相同的书
We even like the same books.
这幅画真可怕
There's a scary painting.
等等
Wait a minute.
我记得好像被这幅画给吓过
I think I've been scared by that painting before.
说起来  这地方看起来真眼熟
You know what? This whole place looks familiar.
我一定曾经来过这里
I have definitely been in this apartment.
我看过这棵古怪的植物
I know I've seen this weird plant before.
它上次也是这样刺我
It did that the last time!
噢  天啊 我跟这个女的约会过
Oh,my God. I've gone out with this girl before.
没错  我们在这沙发上做过爱
Yeah! We had sex on this couch!
然后在那张椅子上  还有  不对
And then on that chair,and.. No.
不对  没有在这里
No,we didn't do it here..
这倒是很奇怪  看起来超适合的
which is weird,because it seems like a perfectly good place.
这就是原因
That's why.
嘿  麦克
Hey,Mike.
很抱歉这样跑过来  我可以进来吗
Sorry to just drop by like this. Can I come in?
当然
Sure.
你是谁呢
Who are you?
我是罗斯  菲比在咖啡屋的朋友
I'm Ross. Phoebe's friend from the coffeehouse?
我真的非常需要跟你谈一件事
I really,really need to talk to you about something.
除非
Unless..
你不是要拉我信什么邪教吧
You're not gonna try and get me to join a cult,are you?
不是  没啦  因为
No.  No,it's just,
你长得很像那种人
you have that look.
该死的超级发型
Damn Supercuts!
怎么回事  菲比还好吗
Well,what's up? Is Phoebe okay?
噢  还好  还好
Oh,yeah,yeah.
菲比很好  但是
Phoebe is great. But..
我是个蠢蛋
I'm an idiot,okay?
就在你们出去约会前
Right before you guys went out..
我不小心惹得她很难过
I accidentally got her all upset.
难怪她不对劲
That's why she was weird.
是的  是啊  我
Yes. Yeah,I..
我说了些蠢话
Yeah,I said something stupid
关于她从没有过认真的恋爱关系等等
about her never having had a serious relationship.
但是你应该知道
But you should know,
她是很风趣  很棒的一个人
she is so much fun. A wonderful person.
拜托  请别离开她
Please,don't blow her off.
我不会离开她的
I'm not gonna blow her off.
我才刚跟她说完电话
I just got off the phone with her.
我们明晚要出去约会
We're going out tomorrow night.
我是说  我希望你没有意见
I mean,I hope that's okay with you,
咖啡屋的陌生人
stranger from the coffeehouse.
好吧  那我就不需要再打扰你了
Well,then,I didn't need to bother you.
你
You
以及我打扰的另外4个麦克·汉尼根
or the four other Mike Hanigans I bothered.
等等  等等
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
你刚刚说的是真的吗
Is that true what you said?
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱
Phoebe's never had a serious relationship?
她当然有过
Of course she has.
如果她没有谈过认真的恋爱
If she's never had a serious relationship..
你认为我会到处去广播
do you think I'd go around broadcasting it..
像是无法克制的白痴一样吗
like some kind of unstoppable moron?
但你的确是那样说了
But you did say it.
是的  是的  我是说了
Yes. Yes,I did.
而且我还会说
And I will also say..
我接下来要说的
what I'm about to say..
面对面地
visavis..
以下的话
the following.
菲比从未谈过认真的恋爱
Phoebe has never had a serious relationship..
自从
since..
她超级认真的恋爱关系
her superserious relationship..
和  维克莱分手之后
with.. Vikram.
维克莱  怎么  那是真的名字
Vikram?  What? That's a real name.
停停吧
Stop it!
为什么不派我去德克萨斯州呢
Why couldn't they have sent me to Texas?
七点钟
Seven o'clock.
或许我该去健身房
Maybe I'll hit the gym.
少来了  还是看色情频道好了
Who am I kidding? Payperview porn.
不要打扰  不要打扰  惊喜吧
Do not disturb! Do not disturb!  Surprise!
莫妮卡  一切都还好吧
Monica?  Is everything all right?
是啊  一切都很好  我刚刚
Yeah,everything's great. I was just..
在看一些常规的电视节目
watching some regular television there.
真是令人开心的小惊喜
What a pleasant surprise.
我去梳洗一下  好吗
I'm gonna go freshen up,okay?
好的  亲爱的
Okay,honey.
好险啊
That was close.
喂  嘿  瑞秋  是我
Hello.  Hey,Rach,it's me.
我刚到钱德勒的房间
Okay,I just got to Chandler's room,
然后看到他
and I caught him..
正在自慰
molesting himself.
那画面可不是很好看
That couldn't have been pretty.
但你知道的  男人常那样做的
But you know,guys do that.
是吗  但是  很奇怪的是
Yeah? Well,the weird part is..
他看的是鲨鱼攻击影片
he was getting off.. to a sharkattack show!
好恶  是的
No!  Yes!
钱德勒竟然在看鲨鱼色情片
Chandler watches shark porn!
在看鲨鱼的时候 是啊
While watching sharks?  Yeah.
你确定他是在做那档事吗
Are you sure that's what he was doing?
你知道我看他那样
You know how many times I've seen him
跳起来多少次了吗
jump up like that?
相信我  我知道他在做什么
Believe me,I know what he was doing.
天啊  鲨鱼
Man! Sharks!
我就知道那家伙有地方不对劲
I always knew there was something weird about that dude.
你发誓过无论如何都要爱他的
You promised to love him no matter what.
"无论如何"意思是像如果他得病
"What" means,like,if he gets a disease
或者杀了人什么的
or kills someone.
而不是如果  他把小弟弟放到鲨鱼嘴里
Not if he gets his jollies to Jaws.
其实  亲爱的  男人是很不一样的
You know what,honey? Guys are just different.
他们喜欢一些我们无法理解的东西
They like things that we can't understand.
我曾经约会过一个男人
I once dated this guy
总喜欢假装
who wanted to pretend..
他是考古学家  而我是
that he was an archeologist,and I was this..
调皮的山顶洞女人
naughty cavewoman
是被他从冰块中解救出来的
who he unfroze from a block of ice.
你是在说我哥吗
Are you talking about my brother?
我装得不像  对不对
I didn't disguise that very well,did I?
我昨晚跟一个女孩子出去
I went out with this girl last night.
到一半的时候才发现
Halfway through our date I realized..
我已经跟她上过床了
I already slept with her.
你已经跟全纽约的女人上过床了
You've slept with all the women in N.Y.,
现在又开始新的一轮吗
and now you're going around again?
那不是最奇怪的地方
That's not even the weird part.
她竟然不记得跟我上过床了
She didn't remember sleeping with me!
你也不记得跟她上过床啊
You don't remember sleeping with her.
但是她应该要记得我的
But she should remember sleeping with me.
我可是很令人难忘的
I am very memorable!
你们知道的  我们怎么会知道呢
You guys know.  How do we know?
我们又没跟你上过床
We've never slept with you.
那是谁的错呢
And whose fault is that?
又没有什么大不了的
What's the big deal?
你忘了  她忘了
You forgot,she forgot.
或许那晚你床上表现不佳  嘿
Maybe you were having an off night.  Hey!
我的床上表现从不会不佳  好吗
I never have an off night. Okay?
虽然有时候如果我吃太饱
Although,sometimes if I'm a little bloated,
可能就不会觉得很性感
I don't feel that sexy.
但是即使是那样  我都比别人强
But even then,I'm better than most!
亲爱的  你何不就此释怀
Honey,why don't you just let it go
再约她出去呢
and ask her out again?
你们都是荡货
You're both so slutty,
你们根本都不记得跟谁上过床
you don't remember who you slept with.
你们是天生的一对
You're made for each other.
真有趣
Interesting.
好吧  我会再跟她出去
Well,I'll go out with her again
然后忘了过去
and I'll try to get past it.
不能吃盐  会胀气
No salt! Bloaty!
乔伊 干嘛
Joey?  What?
你不会也觉得鲨鱼很性感吧
You don't think sharks are sexy,do you?
不会
No.
等一下  等等 小美人鱼是鲨鱼吗
Wait a minute. Wait,what was the Little Mermaid?
门开着的
It's open!
麦克打电话来了  我们要再约会了
Mike called! We're going out again!
一件小事  我去找麦克谈过
Quick thing. I went to talk to Mike.
什么
What?
你做  你做了什么  罗斯
What did you..? What did you do,Ross?
噢  天啊  光这样你就生气了
Oh,boy. You got mad at that part.
我过去找他  告诉他
I went over there,you know,to tell him how..
你是个很棒的人  但是
How great you are. But..
嗯  你知道我的  话太多了
Well,you know me. Blahblahblah.
我最后竟然告诉他  什么
And I ended up telling him that..  What?
你有过六年的恋情
You had a sixyearlong relationship..
跟一个叫做维克莱的人
with a guy named Vikram.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
因为  他好像
Well,he seemed..
有点惊讶  因为我对他说
to bum hard when I told him that
你从未谈过认真的恋情
you'd never been in a serious relationship.
如果你不是刚跟我
If you hadn't just
最好的朋友生下小孩
had a baby with my best friend..
我向魔王发誓
I swear to Lucifer..
一只疯狗正在吃你裤档里的那根东西了
a rabid dog would be feasting on your danglers right now!
我想如果你知道多一点关于维克莱的事
I think you'll feel differently when you know..
你会感觉好多了
a little bit about Vikram.
好的  他是
Okay,he's a..
他是风筝设计师
He's a kite designer.
而且他曾经跟奥普拉约会过
And he used to date Oprah.
我不会跟你一起说谎的  罗斯
I'm not going along with some lie you made up,Ross.
我会跟他老实说 很好
I'm just gonna be honest with him.  Good.
跟他老实说
Just be honest with him.
我没什么好羞耻的  没错
I have nothing to be ashamed of.  No.
好吧  就算我的每段感情
Ok, So I haven't been in a relationship
都没有超过一个月
that lasted longer than a month.
那又如何  我是没有过真正的男朋友
Okay? I haven't had a real boyfriend.
如果他无法接受 那他可以离开
You know? If he can't handle it,then he can leave.
我想他会离开的
Which he will.
而这一切都没有关系
And,you know,that's okay.
我只不过会永远孤单而已
So I'll just be alone forever.
都没关系了  一切都会没事的
You know,all right. It'll be fine. It'll be fine.
我就跟寡妇还有同性恋一起出去玩嘛
I'll go on walking tours with widows and lesbians.
我去开门  好的
I'll get it.  Okay.
让我想想有哪一次开门
I'm trying to remember the last time I opened a door
出现在门口的人不是你
and you weren't there.
菲比  你还好吗
Phoebe,are you okay?
还好  只不过
Yeah. There's just..
有件事你必须知道
There's something you should know.
维克莱刚打电话来
Vikram just called.
在经历25年的婚姻后  真令人惊讶
So it was really a shock after 25 years of marriage..
我的模范父母竟然要离婚
my parents of perfect couple are getting divorced.
我是最难以接受的
I kind took it the hardest..
因为我是家里最小的  当然啰
because I was the youngest.  Sure. Yeah.
你怎么会忘了我是谁
How can you not remember me?
什么
What?
你怎么会忘了我们上过床
How could you not remember that we slept together?
什么  何时 我不知道
What? When?  I don't know!
我真的  真的认为
I really,really think
如果有过  我会记得的
I would remember sleeping with you.
拜托  拜托
Come on,come on.
仔细回想  好吗  就在
Search your brain,all right? It was..
之前某个时候
a certain amount of time ago.
我在这里  你在这里
Ok, I was here. You were here.
我们在这里  这里  这里做爱
We had sex here,here,here..
没在那里
Not there.
想起来了吗  没  一点印象也没有
Anything?  No,it's not ringing any bells.
天啊  女人
My God,woman!
你跟多少人上过床
How many people have you been with
让你根本不记得我
not to remember this?
嘿  海莉 我们真的要修理那个门把了
Hey,Hayley. We really gotta fix that doorknob.
乔伊
Joey?
我跟你上过床
I slept with you!
而且很明显  你记得我
And you obviously remember me!
嘿  表示我还不赖
Hey,I still got it!
所以我们还好嘛
So we're good.
我自己出去
I'll let myself out.
然后我说  维克莱
And I said,"Okay,Vikram..
你不能每次寂寞就打电话给我
you can't just call every time you get lonely. You know.
你已经没有那个资格了
You gave up that right
因为你跟瑞秋上床了
when you slept with Rachel."
瑞秋  她不是才刚生下罗斯的小孩吗
Rachel? I thought she just had a baby with Ross.
是啊  嗯
Yeah,well..
是啊
Yeah.
艾玛的出生证明上
But Emma's birth certificate
或许生父是罗斯
might say "Geller"..
但是她眉眼长得像维克莱
but her eyes say "Mukherjee."
实在太不对了 而且他还吸毒
That is so wrong. And on top of that,he's a glue sniffer?
我知道  但是他打来时
I know. But he calls,
我的心就飞向他了
and my heart goes to him.
你知道的  那个浑蛋
You know,that bastard
是个很会花言巧语的风筝设计师
is one smoothtalking freelance kite designer.
我觉得有更好的人在等着你
I think there's somebody better out there for you.
我是说  你知道的  我
I mean,you know,I'm..
我不是指我  但是
I'm not saying me,but..
或许  是我
Maybe.. me.
而且你不用担心我会吸毒
And you don't have to worry about gluesniffing with me.
虽然有时候我会闻马克笔的味道
Although,I do smell the occasional Magic Marker.
是啊  反正  我只是
Yeah. Anyway,I just..
我觉得我可以让你幸福
I think I can make you happy.
好吧  我编不下去了  怎么了
Okay,I can't do this.  What's wrong?
根本没有维克莱这个人  罗斯乱扯的
Well,there is no Vikram. Ross made him up.
因为我
Because I..
我从未有过爱情长跑
I really never have been in a longterm relationship.
我从未跟男人同居过
I've never lived with a guy.
从来没有庆祝交往一周年
I've never even celebrated an anniversary.
所以
So..
如果这对你而言太奇怪
If that's too weird for you..
你现在如果想走  我完全可以理解
and you want to leave,I totally understand.
事实上  我要闭上双眼
In fact,I'll close my eyes
让这一切不至于太尴尬
to make it less awkward.
你亲了我
You kissed me.
你不认为我是怪人吗
You don't think I'm a total freak?
不
No.
那  我可不
Look,can I..?
我可不可以认为你有点怪  但又有点酷
Can I think you're a little weird and also cool..
因为你告诉我事情的真相
for telling me the truth
而且让我想亲你
and also want to kiss you?
我想可以吧
I guess so.
我可不可以认为  你亲我真是很酷
Can I think it's cool that you kissed me..
而且我想亲回去
and also want to kiss you again?
有一点担心马克笔的事可以吗
And be a little concerned about the Magic Markers?
当然
Definitely.
我是维克莱
This is Vikram.
嗨  亲爱的  我回来了
Hi,honey,I'm home.
旅途还好吗  很棒
How was your flight?  It was great.
过来坐下吧
Why don't you sit down.
放轻松  舒服点
Get yourself comfortable.
因为我有个小...
Because I have a little..
惊喜要给你
surprise for you.
塔尔萨现在一定是五点
It must be 5:00 in Tulsa..
因为纽约现在是六点[性奋点]
because it's "sex o'clock" in N.Y.C.!
好了  这代表我有多爱你
Okay. This is how much I love you.
大白鲨
The great white..
亲爱的
Honey?
为什么要我看一群鲨鱼游来游去呢
Why am I watching a bunch of sharks swimming around?
这不是  这不是你爱看的吗
Is this..? Is this not the good part?
要我快进到露齿比较多的地方吗
Do you want me to fastforward to something.. toothier?
不  我只是想确定
No,I'm just not sure that
你是不是拿错了录影带
you got the right movie,that's all.
录影店里只有这一卷
This is the only one they had at our video store.
不过他们倒是有一部叫"鳄鱼杀手"的
Though they did have something called Crocodile Killers.
难道你非要鲨鱼不可吗
Or does it always have to be sharks?
为什么我非要鲨鱼不可
Does what always have to be sharks?
听着  我们可以来点别的
Look,we can do something else.
你要我到浴缸里  再用力扭吗
Do you want me to get into the tub and.. thrash?
到底是怎么回事
What's going on?
没关系  没关系的
It's okay. It's okay.
我还是爱你的
I still love you.
让我也参与其中
Let me be a part of this.
是你该让我了解其中的缘由
Let me be a part of this!
我看到你在塔尔萨做的事
I saw what you were doing in Tulsa.
愤怒的鲨鱼让你"性"奋
Angry sharks turn you on!
不  并没有
No,they don't.
那为什么你一边看着他们
Then why were you watching them
一边自慰呢
and giving yourself a treat?
噢  天啊
Oh,my God!
当时你一进门 我就转台了
When you came in,I switched the channel.
我本来只是在看一般的色情片
I was just watching regular porn.
真的吗
Really?
是的  只不过是一些正常  老套
Yes. Just some good,oldfashioned,
美式的女对女爱情动作片
American,girlongirl action.
我想说  我真是太开心了
Can I tell you how happy that makes me?
你是个很棒的老婆
You are an amazing wife.
真的  你太棒了
Really,you are amazing.
我是说  你真的愿意为我这样做
I mean, You were actually gonna do this for me?
你哪里来的力量和谅解
Where do you find the strength and the understanding
去这样做呢
for something like that?
因为我现在非常  非常地醉
I'm very,very drunk right now.
通常  我会去跟她搭讪的
Ordinarily,I would talk to her,
但是我的自信已经动摇了
but my confidence is shaken.
我有跟她上床吗  我没有跟她上床吗
Did I sleep with her? Did I not sleep with her?
或许该是你反省的时候了
Maybe this is a wakeup call.
检讨你的整个约会态度
You know,about your whole dating attitude.
你已经三十好几了
You're in your 30s
却没有谈过一段长期的恋爱
and you have never been in a longterm relationship.
女人从一个换到另一个
Here you go from woman to woman..
没有意义的关系
meaningless experience
换到另一段没有意义的关系
to meaningless experience.
从来不去担心
Never even worrying
那些恋情无法发展到谈婚论嫁的阶段
that it doesn't turn into something more serious.
你说的没错  我爱死我的人生了
You're right. I love my life!
事实上  我跟她上过床了
I actually did sleep with her.